- 안녕!
- 어서 와!
-Hi!
-Hey!
내 임신 축하 파티에
몇 명이나 와?
So, what's the final head count
on my baby shower?
20명 정도
직장 사람 몇 명은 바쁘대
About twenty. Couple people
from work had something else to do.
니 여동생들도 못 온대
Your sisters called and can't make it.
뭐? 술과 남자가 없는 파티에
What? You mean they're not coming
to a social event..
걔네가 빠진다구?
놀랄 일이구만
where there's no men and no booze?
That's shocking.
상관없어, 엄마만 오시면 돼
I don't care, as long as my mom's here.
- 아, 맞다, 너희 엄마
- 왜? 엄마 안 오셔?
-Oh, my God. Your mother.
-What? My mom's not gonna be here?
정말 못 오신다면 초대 안한거랑
너무 우연의 일치다
Well, given that we forgot to invite her,
it would be a big coincidence if she was.
무슨 소리야!
My God!
피비가 연락 담당이었어
Phoebe was in charge
of the invitations.
내가 엄마가 없어서
자꾸 잊어버려...
I don't have a mother.
So often I forget..
그만 해!
Oh, give it a rest.
그래서 내 임신 축하 파티에
엄마가 안 오신다구?
So my mother is not coming
to my baby shower?
응
No.
우리 엄마도 안 오셔
Neither is mine.
우리가 지금 전화해 볼게
넌 집에 가서 준비나 해
We'll take care of it. We'll call her.
You go home and get ready.
꼭 오시도록 만들어
나한텐 중요해, 내 엄마라구
Make sure she comes.
It's important. It's my mom.
- 알아, 엄마 전화번호가 뭐지?
- 몰라
-I know. What's her number?
-I don't know.
어서 가, 내 전화번호부에 있어
Go. I have it in my book. Go.
니가 연락 담당인데
왜 내가 전화하고 있지?
If you're in charge of invitations,
why am I calling her?
여보세요?
안녕하세요 모니카예요
Hello, Mrs. Green!
Hi, it's Monica Geller.
- 오, 안녕, 모니카
- 네
-Oh, hello, Monica.
-Hi.
저희가 오늘 즉흥적으로
레이첼 임신축하 파티를
It's last-minute, but we've decided
to throw an impromptu..
- 하기로 했거든요
- 내 딸들 말로는
-baby shower for Rachel today.
-My daughters told me..
그 즉흥 파티 초대를
한달 전에 받았다던데
when they received their impromptu
invitations a month ago.
- 실은, 정말 죄송해요
- 뭐가 죄송해?
-Okay, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
-For what, dear?
나 초대 안한거
아니면 거짓말 한 거?
For not inviting me,
or for lying about it?
정말 엉덩이에 진땀 난다
Oh, my God! My ass is sweating.
전부 다 정말 죄송해요
I'm sorry for everything.
Really, I mean..
이것저것 준비할 게 많다 보니
there's a lot of planning
in a baby shower.
가끔 잊어버리는 것도
생기네요
You know, things get
overlooked and..
피비 엄마는 자살하셨대요
Phoebe's mother killed herself.
왜? 초대 못 받아서?
Why? Did you forget
to invite her too?
농담도 잘 하시네요
Oh, you're so funny.
제발 꼭 오세요
4시에 시작해요
Please, please, can you come?
It starts at 4:00.
- 알았다, 그럼 4시에 보자꾸나
- 고맙습니다
-Well, all right. I'll see you at 4.
-Thank you.
- 3시 아니었어?
- 내가 미쳐!
-Isn't it at 3?
-Son of a bitch!
프렌즈 시즌 8
'임신 축하 파티'
조이! 농구 한 판 할까?
Hey, Joe! Wanna shoot some hoops?
나 이번엔
키 큰 애 방어 안 할거야
And for the record, I am not
covering the tall one this time.
그 여자애 별로 안 커
Fine, but she's not that tall.
못 가, 연습해야 해
게임쇼 사회자 뽑는 오디션 있어
I can't go. I'm practicing. I got an audition
to be the host of a new game show.
- 멋지다!
- 대단한데!
-Cool!
-Great!
낮에는 드레이크 라모레이 박사
If I get it, by day
I'll be Dr. Drake Ramoray.
밤에는 조이 트리비아니 쑈우!
But by night I'll be Joey Tribbiani!
너한테 딱이다!
니 이름을 건 프로를 하다니!
You'll be perfect for this!
That's already your name!
알아
I know. I know.
드라마는 좀 불안정하니까
이 쇼 맡으면 좋을텐데
It'd be great if I got this because you
never know what could happen on a soap.
하지만 평생 게임쇼를
진행할 수도 있지
But I could be
a game-show host forever.
어떤 사람은 75년이나
자기 프로를 진행하잖아
Like that Bob Barker guy. He's been doing
The Price is Right for 75 years.
처음 25년은 시청률이
낮았대
I bet the ratings weren't good
for the first 25.
그땐 텔레비전이 없었으니까
You know, before there was television.
근데 게임이 진짜 복잡해
But the problem,
this game is really complicated.
'헝그리 헝그리 히포'도
복잡하다고 했는데
Come on. You said the same thing
about Hungry Hungry Hippos.
지난주에 벤도 이겼잖아
And last week, you beat Ben.
솔직히 말하면
Yeah. I have to be
honest with you guys.
벤이 일부러 져준 거야
He kind of let me win.
2시간 후에 오디션인데
게임을 이해도 못했어
The audition's in a couple hours,
and I don't understand the game.
도와줄까?
Do you want some help?
정말? 그럼 좋지
너희가 참가자 해라!
Oh, really? That'd be great.
Hey, you guys can be the contestants!
여중생들한테 지는 건
담에 하자
We can lose to junior-high girls
some other time.
좋아, '물먹이기' 게임 시작!
All right. Let's play Bamboozled!
- '물먹이기'?
- 응, 이름 멋지지?
-Bamboozled?
-Yeah. Isn't that a cool name?
- 응!
- 아니!
-Yeah!
-No!
자, 첫 번째 참가자
로스 겔러입니다
All right. Okay.
Our first contestant is Ross Geller.
간단히 자기 소개를 해주시죠
Tell us about yourself, Ross.
저는 고생물학자구요
뉴욕에 삽니다
Well, I'm a paleontologist.
I live in New York.
또 벤이라는 아들이 있구요
벤, 안녕! 그리고...
I have a son, Ben. Hi, Ben! And..
간단히 하라니까요
챈들러씨도 소개 부탁합니다
I said, a little bit, Ross.
How about you, Chandler?
전 헤드헌터입니다
구소련의 과학자들을
I'm a headhunter. I hook up
out-of-work Soviet scientists..
불한당 국가에 팔아 넘기죠
헤이, 라스푸틴
with rogue Third World nations.
Hi, Rasputin.
대단합니다!
그럼, 챈들러씨 먼저 하죠
Excellent! Let's play!
Chandler, you'll go first.
- 콜롬비아 수도는?
- 보고타
-What is the capital of Colombia?
-Bogota.
'바고타'지만 맞다고 치겠습니다
It's Bogota, but close enough.
차례를 로스에게 넘기거나
왱고 카드를 선택할 수 있습니다
You can either pass your turn to Ross
or pick a Wicked Wango Card.
- 왱고 카드가 뭐죠?
- 제가 알아야 하는 거군요
-What does a Wicked Wango Card do?
-I should know that.
봅시다, 잠깐만요
Let's see. One moment, please..
왱고 카드란 위 또는 아래로
가는 걸 결정하는 겁니다
Here we are. A Wicked Wango Card
determines if you go higher or lower.
어디서 위나 아래로 가는데요?
Higher or lower than what?
- 참 당황스럽군요!
- 게임이 좀 허접하지?
-This is embarrassing!
-Can you believe how lame this is?
죄송하지만 참가자끼리는
이야기할 수 없습니다
I'm sorry. I don't believe contestants
are allowed to talk to each other.
스트리퍼는 5시까지 온대
잘 됐지?
I told the stripper to be here at 5.
That's good, right?
스트리퍼를 불렀어?
이 파티에 안 어울리지 않아?
You ordered a stripper for the shower?
That is inappropriate.
왜? 아기 옷 입고 올건데
Why? He's gonna be dressed as a baby.
레이첼 어머니
와주셔서 정말 감사해요
Oh, hi, Mrs. Green.
I'm so glad you could make it.
저희가 얼마나 죄송한 지
모르실 거예요
Thank you so much. We're so sorry.
We could not feel worse about it.
알게 해 봐
Try.
내 딸 저깄네!
There's my little girl!
- 아직도 화나셨나 봐
- 그러게
-She's still mad.
-Yeah, I know.
잘 됐지? 수다 떨어줄
사람 하나 줄었잖아
Isn't it great? One less
person to make small talk with.
안녕하세요?
Hey, how are you?
응, 좋아, 좋아
Yeah, yeah. Okay, okay.
피비, 너한테도 화내시는 거야
신경 안쓰여?
Phoebe, Sandra's mad at you too.
It doesn't bother you?
두 번이나 사과했잖아
더 이상은 나도 못해
We've apologized twice.
I can't do any more than that.
사람들이 너한테 화내는 거
싫어하는 거 아는데
You hate it when people
are mad at you..
그냥 넘길 줄도 알아야 해
but you just have
to be okay with it.
좋아, 그럴게
Okay. I can do that.
- 엉덩이에 파우더 좀 발라야겠다
- 그래
-I gotta go powder my ass.
-Oh.
얼굴 좀 봐라!
꼭 고등학교 때 같네
Look at that face! Just like when
you were in high school.
모르는 사람이었으면
사고친 치어리더인 줄 알겠다
If I didn't know better, I'd say
you were a cheerleader in trouble.
- 나랑 차나 한 잔 하자
- 그래요
-Come, let's get some tea.
-Okay.
이런!
이제 3주밖에 안 남았네
Oh, my! Look at that.
Only three weeks to go.
보모는 따로 구했니?
가정부한테 맡기면 안돼
Did you pick a nanny? If you use your
housekeeper, it will split her focus.
보모 안 쓸 거예요
가정부도 없고요
Actually, I'm not gonna use a nanny.
And I don't have a housekeeper.
원시인이 따로 없구나
It's like you're a cave person.
보모는 있어야 돼
일이 얼마나 많은데
You must get a nanny. You don't
know how overwhelming it will be.
너 어릴 때 K부인 있었잖아
When you were a baby, I had Mrs. K.
그 아줌마 정말 좋았는데
스페인어도 가르쳐 주고
Mrs. K! Oh, yeah, she was sweet.
She taught me Spanish.
아직도 기억 나요
I actually think
I remember some of it.
'너희 엄마는 미쳤나 봐'
Tu madre esta loca.
참 좋은 사람이었지
Such a sweet woman.
결국 우리 가족의 일원이
되었잖니?
And more important,
she became a part of our family.
맞아요
근데 K가 무슨 약자였죠?
That's right, Mrs. K.
What did that K stand for?
내가 어떻게 알아?
그냥 보모였잖아
I have no idea, dear.
She was the nanny.
힘들어도 사람 쓸 능력이 안돼요
As great as she was,
I can't afford that.
미안, 누구나 전남편한테
돈 받는 건 아닌데
I'm sorry. Sometimes I forget
not everyone has alimony.
- 오, 레이첼!
- 왜요?
-Oh, Rachel!
-What?
좋은 생각이 났다!
내가 너랑 같이 사는거야!
I just had a great idea!
I'm gonna come live with you!
네? 뭐라구요?
What? What?
내가 우리 딸한테
이런 일을 해주게 되다니
Oh, I'm so happy I'm gonna
do this for my little girl.
널 좀 보렴
눈에 눈물이 고였구나
Look at you.
You have tears in your eyes.
네, 그러네요
Yes, yes, I do.
로스가 앞서고 있군요
Ross, you're in the lead.
다른 질문을 받겠습니까? 아니면
벌칙바퀴를 돌리겠습니까?
Would you like to take another question
or spin the Wheel of Mayhem?
벌칙바퀴는 오늘 내 편이
아닌 것 같아요
The Wheel has not been
my friend tonight, Joey.
다른 질문 주세요
I'll take another question.
네, 좀 힘든 문제입니다
숨을 죽이고 들으세요
Okay. This is gonna be tough.
Hold your breath.
괜찮아요, 얼른 하세요
It's okay. I'm ready.
대답할 때까지
진짜 숨을 멈추는 문제야
You gotta hold your breath
until you answer.
말도 안돼! 숨을 어떻게...?
This is ridiculous! He's not gonna hold his..
다음은 무엇에 관한 공포증일까요?
트리스카...
Okay. What do you have a fear of if
you suffer from this phobia? Triska..
뭐 이런 단어가 다 있냐?
Holy cow. That's a big word. Trisk..
이거 어떻게 읽는거냐?
Look at this. How do you say that?
- 어디 봐
- 이거
-Let me see that.
-This one right here.
- 트리스카이데카포비아
- 트리스킷(스낵 종류) 공포증!
-Triskaidekaphobia.
-Fear of Triscuits!
- 땡! 숫자 13 공포증입니다
- 트리스킷 공포증이라구?
-No! No. Fear of the number 13.
-Fear of Triscuits?
비스킷 모서리가
얼마나 날카로운데
It's possible.
They have really sharp edges.
챈들러씨 차례입니다
Chandler, you're up.
잠깐, 천사 카드를 사용하면
한 번 더 할 수 있죠?
I'm entitled to use my Angel Pass
for a free turn.
네, 근데 기회는 딱 한 번이니
잘 생각하세요
Yes, yes. But you can only use
it once, so choose wisely.
어렵다
This is tricky.
이기고 있어도 황금 원숭이에서
한 번 더 하고 싶은데
I mean, I am in the lead, but I would
love another shot at the Golden Monkey.
- 이 게임 엉터리야!
- 니가 지니까 그러는 거지?
-This game makes no sense!
-You're upset because you're losing.
로스, 이런 거 하고 있는
우리 모두 얼간이들이야
Oh, come on, Ross.
I think we're all losers here.
제 천사 카드는
나중에 쓰겠습니다
I would like to hang
on to my Angel Pass please.
바퀴를 돌리거나
구글 카드를 쓸 수 있습니다
You can either spin the Wheel
or pick a Google Card.
글쎄요, 잠깐만요
맘대로 하세요
Let me think, let me think.
Oh, I don't care.
꼭 선택하셔야 합니다
You must choose.
- 아무거나, 어차피 마찬가지니까
- 선택하라니까, 바보야
-Either. It makes no difference.
-Choose, you jackass.
- 카드 쓸게요
- 네, '다 내놔' 카드를 골랐군요!
-I'll take a card.
-You picked the Gimme Card!
- 로스의 점수를 다 가져옵니다!
- 뭐라구?
-You get all of Ross' points!
-What?
야, 이거 재밌다!
This game is kind of fun!
지금 이게 말이 된다고 생각해?
You don't think it's crazy that
you get my points..?
참가자들은 서로 말하면
안됩니다
The contestants aren't supposed
to speak to each other.
선물 풀어볼래?
Now, do you wanna start
opening presents..
사람들이 빨리 끝내고
싶어하는 거 같아서
because it seems like people
are getting itchy to leave.
여기서 사람들이란
바로 나야
And when I say people,
I mean me.
- 우리 엄마 왜 초대했어?
- 뭐?
-Why did you invite my mother?
-What?
우리랑 같이 살면서
아기를 돌봐주시겠대
She wants to move in with me and Ross
to help take care of the baby.
- 얼마 동안이나?
- 8주
-For how long?
-Eight weeks.
엄마가 좋긴 하지만
같이 점심 먹기도 힘든 사람이야
I love my mother, but, my God,
a long lunch with her is taxing.
나 같으면 너네 엄마랑
같이 사는거 영광일텐데
I'd be honored if she wanted
to live with me.
안 들리셔, 더 크게 말해
She can't hear you.
이제 어쩌지?
What am I gonna do?
같이 살기 싫으면
싫다고 말씀드려
If you don't want her to move
in with you, just tell her.
그래
곧 아기 엄마도 될 건데
You're right.
I'm about to have a baby.
엄마가 소파에서 주무시는 거
싫다고 해야겠다
I can say I don't want
her sleeping on my couch.
그럼 내 침대에서 주무시겠다고
하겠지? 절대 안되지
She'll wanna sleep in my bed.
This can't happen.
맞아
That is right.
같이 살기 싫다고 말씀드려
Tell her you don't want her
to live with you.
절대 꺾이면 안돼!
Do not take no for an answer.
잘됐다!
이제 레이첼한테 화내실거야!
This is great! Now she's
gonna be mad at Rachel!
그때 내가 끼어 들어서
엄청 착한 딸 노릇을 해야지
And I'm just gonna swoop in there and
be like the daughter she never had.
제발, 그러지 마
Oh, honey, you have
to let it go.
알았어
Okay.
사과를 왜 안 받아주는거야?
Who doesn't accept an apology?
간단하잖아
I mean, it's just so simple.
"정말 죄송해요"
"괜찮다, 모니카"
"I'm sorry, Sandra."
"That's okay, Monica.
"다 용서할게"
I forgive you.
"그리고 너 정말 예쁘구나"
And by the way, you're very pretty."
챈들러가 새삼 존경스럽다
I have new respect for Chandler.
자, 여러분!
선물 풀어볼 시간이에요!
All right, everybody!
It's time to open the presents!
맞아요! 제일 먼저
Yes! The first gift
that Rachel opens..
아기 할머니의 선물부터
풀어보죠
should be from the grandmother.
왜냐면 이 방에서 가장 중요한
분이니까요! 아니 이 세상에서!
Because you're the most important
person in this room! And in the world!
난 선물을 준비 못했어
늦게 초대를 받아서 말이야
I don't have a gift because I wasn't
invited until the last minute.
그렇게 사방에 알려줘서
고맙다, 얘야
But thank you so much, dear, for
bringing that to everybody's attention.
그럼 덜 중요한 사람들
선물을 풀어보죠!
How about you less important people?
Let's open your presents!
- 선물 안 주셔도 괜찮아요
- 실은 이미 준 거지
-It's okay that you didn't get a gift.
-I kind of did.
바로 8주 동안의 내 서비스
Me! Eight weeks of me.
엄마, 실은 저 혼자도
할 수 있어요
Okay. See, Mom,
the truth is, I can do this on my own.
물론 잘 하겠지
I know you're gonna be a terrific mom.
그래도 처음엔 도움이 필요해
But you need help at the beginning.
진짜 혼자 할 수 있어요
내가 할 수 있다구요
I know what I'm doing.
I can handle it.
정말? 트윙클스 기억 나니?
Really? Remember Twinkles?
그건 햄스터구요, 설마 아기를
청소기로 빨아들이겠어요?
He was a hamster.
I'm not gonna vacuum up my baby!
어서 와, 레이첼
선물 시간이라니까!
Okay, come on, Rach.
It's present time!
파티에 좀 집중해
You're the glue holding
this party together.
분위기 썰렁해지지 않게
It's kind of falling apart here.
- 와, 이거 봐!
- 와우!
-Oh, look!
-Wow!
이건 직장 동료들이 준 거야
This is from your friends at work.
어머나! 와우!
이거 뭔지 알겠다
Oh, my gosh! Oh, wow!
Oh, I know what this is.
잠깐만
Wait a minute.
뭔가 이상한데?
That can't be right.
이거 아기한테
맥주 먹이는 깔대기야?
Is that a beer bong for a baby?
얘, 그건 유축기야
Darling, that's a breast pump.
그냥 추측해본 거, 알죠?
암 튼 고마워요
Did I say I was done guessing?
Okay, thank you for that.
와우! 이건 또 뭐지?
Oh, wow! What's this?
- 기저귀 마법사야
- 새 기저귀 뽑아쓰는 거구나!
-It's a Diaper Genie.
-It dispenses clean diapers!
더러운 거 버리는 거야
It's where you put dirty ones.
그냥 밖에 쓰레기통에
버리면 안돼?
Why don't you take it outside
and throw it in a dumpster?
- 하루에 열 번씩 그렇게 할 거니?
- 하루에 열 번이나 해야 돼요?
-You're gonna do that 10 times a day?
-What, it goes 10 times a day?
애한테 인도 음식이라도
먹이는 거야?
Are we feeding this baby Indian food?
아기들은 원래 다 그래
No, dear. That's what babies do.
레이첼, 엄마 말씀 들어
현명한 말씀만 하시잖니
Rachel, listen to your mother.
She is very smart.
그리고 쓰레기 버리러 간 동안
애는 어떻게 할 거니?
What will you do with the baby
while you trot out to the garbage?
글쎄, 기저귀 가는 테이블에
두면 안돼요?
I don't know,
I'd leave it on the changing table?
- 왜? 내가 뭘 어쨌는데?
- 아기는 절대 혼자 두면 안돼
-What? What did I do? What did I do?
-You can't leave a baby alone.
물론 나도 알지!
Of course, I know that!
아기는 물론 절대 혼자 두면
안되지
Of course you never leave
a baby alone.
왜냐면
안전하지 않으니까
It would..
She wouldn't be safe.
내가 있어 줘야지
바보 엄마라도
Not as safe as she would be
with me, the baby dummy.
지금은 선물 풀어 보기가
좀 부담스러워서
Opening the presents is a little
overwhelming right now.
조금 있다가 풀어 볼게요
I'm gonna maybe open
them all a little bit later.
다들 와줘서 고마워요
선물도요
Thank you for coming,
for the gifts..
- 바구니도 예쁘네
- 그건 아기 요람이야
-and this basket is beautiful.
-It's actually a bassinet.
엄마, 제발 같이 있어주세요
Okay, Mommy, don't ever leave me.
다음 대사가 나오는 영화는?
"냄새나는 배지 따윈 치워!"
In what film would you hear this line:
"We don't need no stinking badges!"
- 시에라 어머니의 보물!
- 거꾸로 말하면 보너스가 있습니다
-Treasure of the Sierra Madre!
-Correct! Backwards Bonus.
- 보물의 어머니 시에라!
- 맞았습니다!
-Madre Sierra the of Treasure!
-Yes!
뭐? 그런 걸로 보너스를 줘?
What? There's extra points for that?
않아 옳지 그건!
Fair not that's!
'황금진흙 오두막'으로 가는
사다리를 타겠습니다!
I'd like to go up the Ladder of Chance
to the Golden Mud Hut!
- 좋아요, 몇 칸 가시겠습니까?
- 여섯 칸!
-Wise choice. How many rungs?
-Six!
- 무슨 소리인지 아시죠?
- 배고픈 원숭이!
-That noise can only mean one thing.
-Hungry Monkey!
- 왱고 카드 주세요
- 듣고 푸는 문제입니다
-I'd like a Wicked Wango Card.
-It's an audio question.
이 TV 주제가의 제목은?
Name this television theme song:
어, 나 알아요
잠깐만요
Oh, my God. I know this.
Give me a second.
- '시간거북이'한테 말해 보셔!
- 시끄러!
-Tell it to the Time Turtle!
-Shut up!
- "내 사랑 지니"!
- 네! 다시 선두입니다!
-"I Dream of Jeannie"!
-Yes! Back in the lead!
바퀴 돌릴게요
I'd like to spin the Wheel.
제발 좀!
Oh, come on!
'초특급 고속'전입니다
Super Speedy Speed Round.
- 깡충 보너스 있어요?
- 물론이죠
-Is there a Hopping Bonus?
-Of course.
- 두 초점 안경을 발명한 사람은?
- 벤자민 프랭클린!
-Who invented bifocals?
-Ben Franklin!
정답입니다!
영국 최장의 왕국은?
Correct. Which monarch ruled
Great Britain the longest?
빅토리아 여왕!
Queen Victoria!
문제 사이에 다리를 안 바꿨으니
깡충 보너스는 없습니다!
You forgot to switch legs between
questions. No Hopping Bonus!
매번 잊어버리네!
Every time!
- 네, 이제 챈들러 차례입니다
- 구글 카드 쓸게요
-Yeah. Now over to Chandler.
-I'd like a Google Card.
- 정말이죠?
- 네! 아뇨! 구글!
-Are you sure?
-Yes! No! Google!
와우! 축하합니다, 로스씨!
왜냐면, 챈들러씨는
Oh, my God! Congratulations, Ross!
Because, Chandler..
- 물먹었습니다!
- 안돼!
-you've been Bamboozled!
-No!
- 앗싸!
- 이 게임 정말 최고다!
-Yes!
-This is the best game ever!
내가 필요한 만큼
있어줄 거죠?
You'll stay as long as I need you?
- 그럼
- 난 진짜, 바보 아니에요
-Of course.
-I swear I'm not an idiot.
임신과 출산에 대한 책은
죄다 읽었다구요
I read books on pregnancy
and giving birth.
단지 출산 후에 관한 책을
안 읽은 거지
I didn't think to read about what
to do when the baby comes.
곧 출산일인데
And the baby's coming..
아는게 하나도 없어요
기저귀 마법사에 토해도 돼요?
and I don't know what to do.
Oh, can I throw up in my Diaper Genie?
얘야, 넌 잘 할거야
Sweetie, you're gonna be fine.
- 어디 가세요?
- 화장실 간다
-Where you going?
-I'm going to the bathroom.
이제 걱정 마라
다 괜찮을 거야
Now, don't worry.
Everything's gonna be okay.
괜찮을 거예요!
It is gonna be okay!
해볼만 했어
Worth a shot.
얼굴이 왜 그렇게 빨갛고
땀이 나?
Hey! Why are you all red and sweaty?
방금 챈들러 물 먹였거든!
I just Bamboozled Chandler!
이상한 짓 아냐
Which is not a sexual thing.
- 파티가 빨리 끝났네
- 모르는 소리
-Well, that was a quick shower.
-Not if you were here.
선물 많이 받았나 보네
Looks like we got a lot of good stuff.
응, 엄마가 가장 좋은
선물을 주셨어
We did. My mom got
us the greatest gift of all.
찰흙놀이 이발소 세트?
A Play-Doh Barbershop?
아니, 8주 동안 우리랑
살아주신대
No. She's going to live
with us for eight weeks.
뭐?
What?
아기를 돌봐주신대!
Yes! She's gonna help us
take care of the baby!
농담이겠지?
You're not serious!
좋은 분이긴 하지만
8주는 같이 못 살아
She's a very nice woman,
but we can't take eight weeks of her.
- 우리 아마 돌아버릴 걸
- 로스, 안녕!
-She'll drive us crazy..
-Hi, Ross!
우리 이제 룸메이트네요!
Hey, roomie!
안녕하세요
제가 PD입니다
Hey, I'm Ray.
I'm the producer of the show.
만나서 반갑습니다
It's a pleasure to meet you, Ray.
이쪽은 던컨과 에린이구요
오디션 도우미입니다
This is Duncan and Erin.
They're gonna help with the audition.
- 좋아요
- 준비되면 하세요
-Right, Ray.
-Whenever you're ready.
안녕하세요, 조이 트리비아니입니다
물먹이기 게임을 시작합니다!
Hello. I'm Joey Tribbiani.
Let's play Bamboozled!
에린, 첫 문제입니다, 하키에서
"위대한 선수"는 누구입니까?
Erin, first question. In hockey,
who is known as "The Great One"?
- 그레츠키
- 정답입니다!
-Gretzky.
-Correct!
왱고 카드를 쓰시겠습니까
바퀴를 돌리시겠습니까?
Want to pick a Wicked Wango Card
or spin the Wheel?
규칙 바뀌었다는 말
못 들으셨어요?
Didn't your agents give
you the revised rules?
그거 다 없앴어요
바퀴랑 카드랑 모두
We've eliminated all that.
No wheel. No cards.
왜요?
Why?
너무 복잡해서
사람들이 못 따라해서요
It was too complicated.
People didn't follow it.
복잡해요? 사다리를 올라가려면
바퀴를 돌리고
Complicated?! Spin the Wheel
to go up the Ladder of Chance..
황금 원숭이 잡으려면
무지개링을 통과하면 되잖아요
through the Rainbow Ring
to the Golden Monkey.
원숭이 꼬리 잡아당기면
패러다이스 연못으로 가구요!
You yank his tail,
and you're in Paradise Pond!
그거 다 없앴어요
Yeah. All that's gone.
이젠 그냥 단순한
묻고 답하기 게임이에요
It's a simple
question-and-answer game now.
그럼, 재미가 없잖아요
Well, what's fun about that?
묻는 말에 대답이나 하는
지루한 게임을 진행하라구요?
You expect me to host a boring game
of people answering questions?
비키니 입은 여성들이
점수판을 들고 서 있을 거예요
Women in bikinis hold up the scores.
얼른 게임 시작합시다!
Let's play Bamboozled!
거실에 기저귀 가는 테이블을
두려고 했는데
So I thought we'd put the
changing station in the living room.
보석 박힌 장식장도 가져오고
그래야 내 미모가
I thought I'd bring in my decorator
because I feel like I'm at my best..
돋보이거든
when surrounded by jewel tones.
어련하시겠어요?
Sure, who doesn't?
오, 그리고 공룡 나부랭이들은
Oh, and all those dinosaur
knickknacks you have..
창고가 더 어울리지 않을까?
they might be more at home
in the garage.
- 저희 창고 없는데요
- 아, 난 쓰레기통 말한 건데
-Well, we don't have a garage.
-Did I say garage? I meant garbage.
무리해서 저희랑
사실 필요는 없어요
You know what? Maybe it's not
absolutely vital that you live with us.
- 레이첼 혼자는 아기 못 키워
- 정말이야, 난 아무것도 몰라
-Well, Rachel needs help with the baby.
-I really do. I don't know anything.
그렇지 않아
I'm sure that's not true.
아니라구?
내가 아기에 대해 뭘 알지?
Oh, no?
Do I know anything about babies?
- 하나도 모르던데
- 심하게 몰라
-No. Not a thing.
-It's frightening.
레이첼이 모르더라도
제가 아니까 괜찮아요
Even if she doesn't
know anything, I do.
제가 가르쳐 줄 거예요
And I'll be there to show her.
레이첼 아빠도 똑같은
소리를 했었어
That's exactly what
Rachel's father told me.
새벽 3시 우유 먹일 시간에
그 사람이 뭐란 줄 알아?
Know what he said
at the first 3 a.m. feeding?
"나 피곤해, 당신 혼자해"
"I'm tired. You take care of it."
나중에 섹스하자고 할 때
내가 그 말을 써먹었지
Which I later said to him
when he wanted to have sex.
전 달라요
Well, I'm not Rachel's dad.
죄송한데, 레이첼 아빠가 좀
바보 같으시잖아요
And no offense,
but he's an ass.
자네 정말 맘에 드네
I do like you, Ross.
전 아들도 있어요
걔 엄마랑은 같이 안 살았구요
I have a son. His mother
and I didn't live together.
제가 데리고 있을 때는
아기를 저 혼자 돌봤어요
When he was with me, I took
care of him all the time, by myself.
- 맞아, 아이가 하나 더 있지?
- 네
-That's true. You do have another child.
-Yeah.
다른 여자랑?
With another woman.
로스, 통제가 안되던가?
Have you no control, Ross?
이야기가 이상하게 가는데요
That's a different issue.
제 말씀은, 제가 우유도 먹이고
The point is, when the baby comes,
I will be there to feed her..
목욕도 시키고 기저귀도 갈고
and bathe her and change her.
제가 다 해주고 싶어요
I want to do all those things.
- 그럼 내가 필요가 없겠네
- 맞아요!
-You don't need me to live with you.
-Yes!
네, 정말 보고 싶을 거예요
Yes. You're gonna be so missed.
- 자넨 훌륭한 아빠가 될 거야
- 훌륭한 할머니가 되실 거예요
-You'll be a great father.
-You'll be a wonderful grandma.
이보세요? 전 아직도
아무것도 모른다구요!
Hello? I still don't know
what the hell I'm doing!
처음엔 다들 그래
Every first-time mother
feels that way.
하나씩 배우게 될거야
너 처음 여기 왔을 때 생각나?
You're gonna pick it up. Hey, you will.
Look, when you first came to the city..
아빠 신용카드나 긁어대는
철부지였잖아!
you were a spoiled, helpless little
girl who used Daddy's credit cards!
그게 이거하고 무슨 상관이야?
I hope you're going
somewhere with this.
지금의 너를 봐
회사의 간부가 됐잖아
Look at you.
You're this big executive.
넌 니가 생각하는 것보다
훨씬 재능이 많아
You are more capable
than you give yourself credit for.
난 니가 정말 훌륭한 엄마가
될 거라고 믿어
I have no doubt you're gonna
be an incredible mother.
- 정말?
- 장담해
-Really?
-I'm telling you.
고마워
Thank you.
그럼 난 가봐야겠다
All right. I'm gonna get going.
아냐, 아가, 나오지 마
No, sweetheart, stay put.
여기 내가 없거니 생각해
실제로도 그런거나 마찬가지고
I'll let myself out. It's like I'm
not here. Which I almost wasn't.
정말 너무 유머러스하세요
도대체 어떻게 해야 돼?
You're just so funny. You're so funny.
What do I do?
그만 해
수 천번 사과했으면 됐어
Nothing. You have apologized
to her, like, a million times.
그런데도 너한테 저렇게
못되게 구시다니
And she's been nothing
but terrible to you.
자기 딸한테 근사한 파티도 열어줬구
좀 지루하긴 했지만
You just threw her daughter a lovely,
albeit slightly boring, shower.
- 그런데도 감사하단 말도 안했어
- 맞아, 니 말이 맞아
-And she hasn't even thanked you for it.
-You know what? You're right.
하고 싶은 말 있으면
다 해버려
If you wanna say anything,
I'd tell her off.
정말?
Really?
좋아, 할게
Okay, I will.
그린 부인?
Mrs. Green?
파티 주최자한테 인사도 안하고
가는 건 좀 무례한 거 아녜요?
It is rude to leave a party without saying
goodbye to the host.
그리고 누가 사과를 하면
받아줘야죠
When someone apologizes to you,
the decent thing to do is to accept it.
고의로 그런 것도 아닌데
What I did wasn't on purpose.
그런데도 저한테 계속
심술궂게 행동하시네요
But what you're doing to me now
is plain spiteful.
- 심술궂다구?
- 네
-Spiteful?
-That's right.
이제 반성하실 때도 됐잖아요
아가씨!
It's time you took a good
look in the mirror, young lady!
할머니!
Old lady!
아줌마!
Lady!
빨리빨리 끝내
Wrap it up. Wrap it up. Wrap it up.
사과하시면 저는 다
용서해 드릴게요
So whenever you're ready to apologize
to me, I will forgive you.
안녕히 가세요
Good day.
다리가 막 후들거려!
I can't feel my legs!
정말 잘 했어!
자랑스럽다
You were fantastic!
I'm so proud of you.
- 그래? 나도 내가 자랑스러워
- 그래야지
-Yeah? I'm proud of me too.
-You should be.
- 나 마실 거 좀 갖다 줄래?
- 그래!
-Could you get me something to drink?
-You got it!
그린 부인? 제가 잘못했어요!
정말 죄송해요
Mrs. Green? Okay, I'm really sorry!
I apologize. If you..
알았어요! 혀 깨물었어요!
Okay! I bit my tongue!
그래도 정말 죄송해요!
But I'm still really sorry!
- 좋아, 준비됐어
- 정말이야?
-Okay, I'm ready.
-You sure?
공부 다 끝내서 이제 빠삭해
I've done my studying,
and I know my stuff.
좋았어, 그럼
All right, then.
레이첼 그린
물먹이기 게임 시작합니다!
Rachel Green,
let's play Bamboozled!
아기 목욕물 온도는
어떻게 재죠?
How do you test the temperature
of the baby's bath water?
- 팔꿈치를 넣어 봐요
- 맞았습니다!
-Put your elbow in it.
-Excellent!
- 낮잠 재우려면 어떻게 눕히죠?
- 뽀송뽀송한 곳에 등쪽으로 눕혀요
-How do you put a baby down for a nap?
-Full, dry, on its back, no loose covers.
딩동댕!
Correct!
깡충 보너스가 있는데
안 받으시는게 좋겠네요
There's a hopping bonus here,
but I don't suggest you take it.
좋아요
Okay.
듣고 푸는 문제입니다
아기가 이 소리를 내면?
This is an audio question. What do
you do when a baby makes this sound:
기저귀가 젖었거나 배가 고프다
Check if it's wet or hungry, burp it.
대단해요! 다음 문제를 풀까요
왱고 카드를 받을까요?
Excellent! Now do you want another
question or a Wicked Wango Card?
- 카드요! 카드 주세요!
- 오, 이런
-A card! A card! I pick a card!
-Oh, I'm sorry.
물먹었습니다!
끔찍한 엄마가 되겠군요!
You've been Bamboozled!
You're gonna be a terrible mother!
우리가 이걸 왜 했는지
잠깐 잊어버렸어!
I've lost sight of why we're doing this!
제발 가지 마
Please don't walk away.
내가 심했어
I've gone too far.